<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on 0x0v1</title>
    <link>https://0x0v1.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on 0x0v1</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>2023. The content of this website is published under [CC-BY-SA license](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/).</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 20:43:39 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://0x0v1.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reverse engineering SuperBear RAT.</title>
      <link>https://0x0v1.github.io/posts/superbear/superbear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 20:43:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0x0v1.github.io/posts/superbear/superbear/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re probably thinking, why is it called SuperBear? Well, here&amp;rsquo;s why:
I spent some time analyzing this attack campaign that was impacting civil society groups and thought it would be a good idea to document the technical analysis for the low-level infosec consumers. You can read our high-level report of the malware campaign here on Interlab&amp;rsquo;s website.
Nethertheless I found this sample to be quite interesting since it utilized some interesting techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Korean Military of Defence&#39;s Mobile Defence Security application</title>
      <link>https://0x0v1.github.io/posts/koreanmnd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 12:52:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0x0v1.github.io/posts/koreanmnd/</guid>
      <description>The Korean Military of Defence&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Mobile Defence Security&amp;rdquo; application (국방모바일보안) The Korean Military has a mandatory phone application for all soldiers. This application is used to support military personnel, staff and contractors to securely enter buildings and reduce the risk of data leaks. At the start of the year, I found two vulnerabilities in this application that would leak GPS locations of user. The Korean Ministry of Defense refused to respond to me or my findings, despite patching the product and speaking to media about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World... Are there hacktivists out there still?</title>
      <link>https://0x0v1.github.io/posts/hello-world/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 14:32:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0x0v1.github.io/posts/hello-world/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to this space, reader. As I embark on creating this dedicated website for myself and my work, I find it both exciting and slightly surreal, given that it is a self-driven endeavor. However, my purpose in establishing this platform is to provide a space where I can document my endeavors and contribute to the advancement of privacy, security, and human rights, ultimately fostering positive change. My goal is to offer valuable resources and support to like-minded individuals who share a common vision of creating a better world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
